isoosi.com 2016-10-13

# Privacy Policy | ISOOSI Web Directory

This Privacy Policy describes the terms of ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc.’s commitment to your privacy.

#### Persons or Parties Covered

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover all visitors to the ISOOSI Web Directory website, all subscribers to lists or newsletters whether paid or unpaid, all members or affiliates whether paid or unpaid, and all customers. Persons who visit or view the ISOOSI Web Directory Inc. website, whether intentionally or unintentionally, whether solicited or unsolicited, are described herein as "Visitors" and are parties to this Privacy Policy. 

Subscribers to ISOOSI Web Directory lists or newsletters are referred to herein as "Subscribers" and are in addition parties to this Privacy Policy as well. 

Persons who promote or recommend ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. websites (e.g. "affiliates") are also covered by this Privacy Policy. 

Finally, anyone who orders, attempts to list their website, or receives a product or service sold specifically by ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. is called a "Customer" herein and is subject to this Privacy Policy by passive acceptance. 

ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. its agents, owners, operators, and employees are referred to collectively herein as the "Website," "Site," and/or "Seller".

#### Persons Excluded From This Website Are Still Covered

In the event that a person excluded from the ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. website because of the Terms of Use, or from denial of service, who nonetheless unlawfully views the ISOOSI Web Directory website, that person remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and is in violation of the Terms of Use.

####  Viewing and/or Use and/or Communication Is Construed As Acceptance Of The Terms Of This Policy 

By visiting the ISOOSI Web Directory website, you are accepting the terms described in this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use and other policies, as noted on this website.

#### About The Personal Information This Website Collects and How It Is Used

ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. websites routinely collect information about visitors, subscribers, members, and customers. This information is obtained in various ways, such as:

##### Visitor, subscriber, member, or customer information obtained from 'registration'

Registration means that the Visitor, Subscriber, Member or Customer takes active, positive steps to communicate information to the ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. website. This can include pages or 'pop ups' where you register for a newsletter or subscribe to a mailing list; it can include your participation in visitor surveys; it can include requesting information from the Website via E-mail, mail, or courier; it may be from joining an affiliate program or other membership organization, paid or unpaid; it may be from ordering a product.

Occasionally complete credit card information may be provided to ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. via fax or a fill-in form, rather than regular secure merchant service processing. This information is kept at the highest level of security and is never divulged to anyone except the merchant service provider or for the purpose of communication with the customer.

#### ONLINE ORDERING

Online ordering via SSL encrypted communication provided by shopping cart services supporting merchant service companies like Visa and Master Card provides information to ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. but does not provide complete credit card numbers. In the process of online ordering, the customer provides, name, address, city, state, E-mail address, phone number, CVS (back of card) number, and occasionally a member password. You should consider all this information available to ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc.. This information is used to deliver the product, but you also approve its use for general solicitation purposes.

#### VISITOR E-MAIL INQUIRIES

Website visitors who wish to communicate with ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. do so under two conditions: one, they give their permission for contact by ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc.; two, they are subject to the general 'SUBMISSION' agreement of this policy. While your E-mail address may or may not be used to solicit you, it is added to ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc.’s general solicitation database.

#### CUSTOMER E-MAIL OR TESTIMONIALS

If you are a customer and send an E-mail to ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc., or if you communicate with ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. by phone or mail, ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. collects information about your communication and by communicating with us, you give your permission to collect, archive, retrieve, and otherwise use any information collected as ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. sees fit.

Any communication which, in its sole discretion, ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. deems to be a testimonial, may be publicized for commercial purposes.

#### INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM VISITOR INTERACTION WITH BANNERS, POPUPS, OR SITE ADVERTISERS

Visitors clicking on banners or pop-ups or hyperlinked advertising, appearing on this and other ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. websites must assume that information is being collected about them. ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. is not responsible for the use of information collected in such a fashion. Visitors must assume that (1) information will be collected, (2) that ‘cookies' will usually be placed on their hard drive, (3) that ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. does not have any control over what happens with this information, (4) that ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. takes no responsibility over the accuracy or content of advertisers, (5) that ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. is not responsible for downloads from third party advertisers that contain viruses or worms or other computer code that causes their computer or software harm, and (6) that ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. assumes no responsibility for the data that is garnered from the click itself or that the advertiser collects.

#### INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM REFERRING E-MAIL OR REFERRING URLS

If you send a friend an email from this or other ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. websites or if you send the URL or one of our pages to a friend, you must assume that some data is collected about your IP address or your E-mail address and that of your friend. You must assume that referred E-mails or Web pages may appear to come from your E-mail. You must accept fully responsibility for referring pages or E-mail to a friend and agree to indemnify this site for any damage, intentional or unintentional that results from said referrals.

#### INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM VOLUNTARY VISITOR, SUBSCRIBER, MEMBER OR CUSTOMER SURVEYS

Unless otherwise specified in the survey, you must assume that any information provided to ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. as part of a survey in which you participate may be used for general solicitation for commercial purposes and that such information will be shared with joint venture partners, affiliates, marketing organization or used by the site itself for product design or solicitation purposes.

#### INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM ELECTRONIC MEANS AND 'COOKIES'

Many Websites, including this one, collect information about your computer, your E-mail address, and your IP address. You must assume that your Web-viewing or Web-use activity is monitored, tracked, and information collected. This information is not usually of a personal nature, but it may help define your viewing habits and product preferences even though the Website may or may not have any idea who you are.

"Cookies" are bits of computer code placed on your hard drive. Websites use these to keep you 'logged in', to keep track of search criteria, to monitor use, and to password protect use of the site or use of products sold by the site. Cookies can also be used to obtain information about your computer configuration or your use of your computer.

Cookies can be used to electronically gather information about you. Again, it may or may not be personal information, but it is information and by using this site you are expressly giving permission to use 'cookies' and to use the information gathered from their use to benefit you. You also give permission to collect, archive, retrieve, and use any information collected for product design, product offers to you, and general commercial solicitation purposes by this site or joint venture partners, affiliates, and marketing organizations.

#### HOW INFORMATION MAY BE USED

The use of information as described below may or may not be how this site customarily uses information that is collected. While actual use of any information collected may be used quite conservatively, you must assume that it is not. You must assume that information collected is shared with other persons or entities for commercial purposes. While this is uncommon in practice, you must assume that it is as you make your decision whether or not to view or interact with this Website. This type of shared information may include your name, address, phone number, E-mail address and buying habits, as well as other information. ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. may use this information for general commercial solicitation or other persons it is sold to, rented to, or shared with.

#### INFORMATION THAT IS NOT SHARED

Credit card information or other financial information is not usually known to ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc.. However, in the event that it is made known, that information is never revealed to anyone except to processing authorities or law enforcement agencies. However, the provider of such information gives express permission to use said information in fraud investigation or for litigation.

#### SPAM

By providing to this Website information that forms the basis of communication with you, such as an E-mail address, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited E-mail or spam from ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. By providing such information, you agree to receive communication from us or other marketing organizations. However, all E-mail communication with you shall contain an 'unsubscribe' link where you may notify ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information from ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. and your name will be removed from the general solicitation database.

#### DATA SECURITY

ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. takes measures to protect its data that contains information related to you. However, as a consideration for viewing this site or interacting with this site in any manner, you waive all claims of any nature against this site concerning the loss, alteration, or misuse of information. You must assume that it is possible for your personal data to be obtained by others, such as "hackers," and used in an inappropriate manner that may cause you harm and that you agree that the site is not responsible for damages to you.

#### REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WITHOUT NOTICE

This Privacy Policy is dynamic. It will continually change. You may not assume that it remains the same and you agree to check the policy each time you visit this or other ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. websites for changes. Unless, in the sole opinion of ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc., this policy changes so drastically as to suggest a posted notification on the site or via E-mail, you will receive no notification of changes to this Privacy Policy nor, under any circumstances, does this site promise notification. Your continued use of this and other ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. websites always evidences your acceptance of the terms this Privacy Policy or any modifications.

#### LATEST UPDATE

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: 07/29/12

#### DISPUTES

As part of the consideration that ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc. requires of the Visitor to view, use, or interact with this site, Visitor agrees to use binding arbitration for any claim, dispute, or controversy ("CLAIM") of any kind (whether in contract, tort or otherwise) arising out of or relating to this purchase, this product, including solicitation issues, privacy issues, and terms of use issues.

Arbitration shall be conducted pursuant to the rules of the American Arbitration Association, which are in effect on the date a dispute is submitted to the American Arbitration Association. Information about the American Arbitration Association, its rules, and its forms are available from the American Arbitration Association, 335 Madison Avenue, Floor 10, New York, New York, 10017-4605. Hearing will take place in the city or county of the Seller.

In no case shall the Visitor have the right to go to court or have a jury trial. Visitor will not have the right to engage in pre-trial discovery except as provided in the rules; you will not have the right to participate as a representative or member of any class of claimants pertaining to any claim subject to arbitration; the arbitrator's decision will be final and binding with limited rights of appeal.

The prevailing party shall be reimbursed by the other party for any and all costs associated with the dispute arbitration, including attorney fees, collection fees, investigation fees, travel expenses.

#### JURISDICTION AND VENUE

If any matter concerning this purchase shall be brought before a court of law, pre- or post-arbitration, Visitor agrees that the sole and proper jurisdiction will be the State and City declared in the contact information below. In the event that litigation is in a Federal Court, the proper court shall be the closest federal court to the Seller's address.

#### APPLICABLE LAW

Visitor agrees that the applicable law to be applied shall, in all cases, be that of the State of Seller.

## Contact Information

ISOOSI Web Directory, Inc.

568 9th Street South, Suite #357, 

Naples, FL 34102
